{
  "3": [
    { "prompt": "I have a mother", "answer": "my mother", "my" },
    { "prompt": "My brother", "answer": "I have a brother", "I" },
    { "prompt": "You have a father", "answer": "your father", "your" },
    { "prompt": "Your sister", "answer": "You have a sister" },
    { "prompt": "He has a wife", "answer": "his wife" },
    { "prompt": "His son", "answer": "He has a son" },
    { "prompt": "She has a husband", "answer": "her husband" },
    { "prompt": "Her daughter", "answer": "She has a daughter" },
    { "prompt": "I have a friend", "answer": "my friend" },
    { "prompt": "My wine", "answer": "I have wine" },
    { "prompt": "You have beer", "answer": "your beer" },
    { "prompt": "Your juice", "answer": "You have juice" },
    { "prompt": "He has water", "answer": "his water" },
    { "prompt": "His coffee", "answer": "He has coffee" },
    { "prompt": "She has a teacher", "answer": "her teacher" },
    { "prompt": "Her student", "answer": "She has a student" }
  ]
}
